joomlaez.com 2010-03-30

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

In today's world of shared information, JoomlaEZ takes great care of protecting your personal information when you are using our Website (<http://joomlaez.com/>) and any products or services provided on the Website. This Privacy Policy details JoomlaEZ's policies relating to your personal information. We may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time for any changes.

Please make sure you read following statement till the end. By using our Website or any products or services provided by JoomlaEZ, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS BELOW, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE WEBSITE OR THE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OFFERED BY THE WEBSITE.

## We respect your privacy

JoomlaEZ will not collect, monitor, use and disclose any personal information about you without your consent. We recognizes that your privacy is very important to you and that you have a right to control your personal information. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously.

JoomlaEZ is committed to protecting your privacy.

## What information do we collect and how do we use it

### Personally identifiable information

Only information you provide JoomlaEZ with directly will be collected, such as through subscribing to various products & services, or identifying yourself when requesting information to be sent to you. For example, when you fill out a request form, we collect the details you enter in order to post information to you. When you answer questions about what you would like to see we keep this information so as to better serve you.

### Emails

From time to time with your permission JoomlaEZ will send you relevant information emails regarding products and services which you have previously registered your interest in. If you are receiving promotional information from JoomlaEZ and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may unsubscribe anytime. 

### Credit card information

If you use a credit card to purchase products and/or services via the Website, information required by transaction such as your name as it appears on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. We does not record or keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions; rather such information is simply passed through to our contracted payment processing vendor. However, We may access such information through the payment processing company to process refunds or adjustments and to the extent necessary in the event of nonpayment or disputed payments, or as may be necessary for JoomlaEZ' compliance, in JoomlaEZ' discretion, with applicable law.

### Cookies

JoomlaEZ uses "cookies" to help enhance your experience on the site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies as the default. Cookies themselves do not contain personal information about you. They simply operate as a unique identifier which helps JoomlaEZ to know what customers find interesting and useful on the website, almost like a continuing questionnaire. JoomlaEZ does not store any personal information inside cookies, although the cookie may identify the user's browser. 

The use of cookies can enhance your experience on the JoomlaEZ site, by remembering information that you have previously given. They can make it easier for you to fill out forms, shop online and can ensure that information provided to you is most relevant to your interests.

### Log files

We and/or our contracted web analytics provider(s) do keep track of the domains from which you access our Site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results of our marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users' movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## How do we store and protect your information

JoomlaEZ will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. In addition, our employees and data processors are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, JoomlaEZ will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information. We encourage you to play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any passwords and account details used on the Website. 

If you have any questions about the security at our Website, please contact us thru [contact page](http://www.joomlaez.com/component/contact/2.html "Contact JoomlaEZ").

## How do you change/update your information

Your trust in JoomlaEZ is very important to us. You are free to update your information at any time directly through our Website. In as much as your information will never be used without your explicit consent, we are not able to update the email address to which you subscribe to JoomlaEZ communications on your behalf.
